<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sandra Sch&amp;ouml;nberger on Sandra Schönberger</title>
    <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sandra Sch&amp;ouml;nberger on Sandra Schönberger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 14:51:17 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Von Aubergine bis Zucker</title>
      <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/projects/finished/tre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 19:47:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/projects/finished/tre/</guid>
      <description>A dictionary about German words with Arabic roots.
This group project was developed during the 2nd semester. Every student picked a word and created an illustration and a poetical text for this word. I picked the word &amp;ldquo;Safran&amp;rdquo;. Since we were not able to meet in person because of the pandemic, we chose the kitchen lithography for our illustrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAST-Test</title>
      <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/projects/finished/due/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 19:47:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/projects/finished/due/</guid>
      <description>Conception, Illustration and designing of the app &amp;ldquo;FAST-Test&amp;rdquo;, which is meant to help stroke patients and relatives.
This project was a group project of a fellow student and me. In order to build a functional and working prototype, we spent a lot of time on the conception, which included personas, user stories and user journeys. We also talked to a neurologist about our app. The design is built very simple to guarantee a fast use without difficulty in case of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Das Reis(e)korn</title>
      <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/projects/finished/uno/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 19:46:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/projects/finished/uno/</guid>
      <description>Conception, illustration and production of the book &amp;ldquo;Das Reis(e)korn&amp;rdquo;
During my 3rd Semester I concepted, illustrated and produced a book about a single rice grain and the journey it has to go on in order to be sold an consumed in Germany. The illustrations series, which comprises 15 pictures, were realized with linocut. My intention was to lead the reader through simple structures and a guiding concept.
Since India is one of the most important exporters for rice, I decided to let the journey start there, more precisely in the state Tamil Nadu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planquadrat</title>
      <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/projects/current/tre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 19:46:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/projects/current/tre/</guid>
      <description>Documentation and exhibition of a photography workshop in my 4th semester in cooperation with street photographer Margret Hoppe.
During the 4th semester I got the opportunity to participate in a photography workshhop. The main goal was to show the beauty and diversity of the city of Münchberg. Every student was assigned a grid square of Münchberg randomly. We spent the whole day taking photos in these grid squares. Subsequently, all photography series were talked about and compiled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glaubenssache</title>
      <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/projects/current/due/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 19:46:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/projects/current/due/</guid>
      <description>Our main focus during the 4th semester was to work with the city of Münchberg and the people living there. As a part of this project, I created a city map on the subject of the diversity of religion in Münchberg.
I mainly worked with photography and illustration. To show the variety of beliefs, I added interviews with inhabitants of Münchberg. I especialliy wanted to include personal stories and experiences to make my project more relatable and understandable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Datenschutz</title>
      <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/dataprotection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 14:52:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/dataprotection/</guid>
      <description>Im Folgenden möchten wir Sie aufklären, wie Ihre Daten von uns verarbeitet werden.
Verantwortlich im Sinne der DSGVO ist:
Sandra Schönberger
Ludwigstr. 27
95213 Münchberg
Sollten Sie per E-Mail mit uns Kontakt aufnehmen, werden die mitgeteilten Daten von uns gespeichert, um Ihr Anliegen zu bearbeiten.
Wir werden die Daten löschen, sobald die Speicherung nicht mehr erforderlich ist oder die Verarbeitung einschränken, falls gesetzliche Aufbewahrungspflichten bestehen.
Betroffenenrechte
Sie haben als betroffene Person, das Recht auf Auskunft, das Recht auf Berichtigung oder Löschung, das Recht auf Einschränkung der Verarbeitung und das Recht auf Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung Ihrer Daten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 14:52:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Angaben gemäß § 5 TMG Sandra Schönberger
Ludwigstr. 27
95213 Münchberg
Kontakt Telefon: +49 15732638571
E-Mail: hello@sandraschoenberger.de
Quelle: Recht24</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Lizenzen</title>
      <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/opensource/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 14:52:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/opensource/</guid>
      <description>Diese Website setzt folgende Komponenten ein, die unter Open-Source-Lizenzen stehen.
This Website makes use of the following components which are distributed under Open Source Licenses.
Manrope Font Copyright 2018 The Manrope Project Authors (https://github.com/sharanda/manrope) This Font Software is licensed under the SIL Open Font License, Version 1.1. This license is copied below, and is also available with a FAQ at: http://scripts.sil.org/OFL ----------------------------------------------------------- SIL OPEN FONT LICENSE Version 1.1 - 26 February 2007 ----------------------------------------------------------- PREAMBLE The goals of the Open Font License (OFL) are to stimulate worldwide development of collaborative font projects, to support the font creation efforts of academic and linguistic communities, and to provide a free and open framework in which fonts may be shared and improved in partnership with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 14:52:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 14:51:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandraschoenberger.github.io/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hello again, my name is Sandra and I’m in the 4th semester of studying communication design at Hof University. I’m 19 years old and originally from a small town near Landshut. In 2020 I finished my A levels and started to study right away. I’ve always loved to be creative and to help people out, therefore communication design was my first choice. And I’m still very happy with my decision. My main emphasis can be found in the sectors of editorial-design, graphic design, social design and photography.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
